

Harsh Shrivastava

Software Developer

+91 797 464 7991

harshushri50@gmail.com

Gurgaon, India

Skills

- Programming Languages -HTML5, CSS, SAAS, javascript, Kotlin, Python.
- Framework React, Next.js.
- Library Redux, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS, Jetpack Compose, ExoPlayer, IMA, Material UI, AntD.
- TOOLS & HOSTING **PLATFORM -** Git, Github, Firebase, Netlify, Postman, Docker, Figma.

Links and Credentials





<u>Github</u>





Website (O) Instagram

Projects

Web

Portfolio Portfolio-Backend

Android Apps

think. Quotes Popular-tweets

Flutter And ML

Farmaid Atulya News App

About

I have **2 years** experience as a **Software Developer**. Developed and launched in-house applications, SDK's, and websites using Kotlin, React.js, Next.js and other technologies, achieving positive user feedback and improved site performance. Played a key role in front-end development for dashboards and contributed to multiple web projects. possesses skills in mobile and web development, and DevOps

Education

2019-2023

 Jaypee University Of Engineering and Technology

Bachelor of Computer Science, Artificial Intelligence

I graduated in January 2023 with a CGPA of 8.4.

Experience



Z1 Tech

Software Developer | Feb 2023 - present

• Flapster and Pixel Perfect: Successfully launched two inhouse applications catering to specific user needs with tailored functionalities.

SDK Development

- Ads Mediation Library: Developed a comprehensive Ads Mediation Library that simplifies the integration of ads from various platforms into a single SDK.
- Functionality: Helps publishers manage and optimize ad placements without needing to individually integrate each ad net- work's SDK.
- Technologies Used: Kotlin, Java
- · Achievements: Enhanced ad revenue by optimizing ad delivery and improving fill rates, resulting in a 20% increase in ad revenue for publishers using the SDK.

Web Development

- Websites: Contributed to the development and maintenance of several key websites, including zltech.com, vdo.ai, woz.ai, and xuno.ai.
- Functionality: These sites serve diverse functions from corporate information to video ad solutions and Al-driven platforms.
- Technologies Used: React.js, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Next.js
- Frontend Development: Played a pivotal role in building the frontend of dashboards for the woz-chatbot and xuno dashboard.
- Technologies Used: Larevel Framework, HTML, CSS, Javascript,React.js
- · Achievements: Enhanced user experience by creating clean, user- friendly interfaces that facilitate efficient data visualization and interaction.



Demotic Technologies PVT. LTD.

Mobile App Developer | Aug 2022 - Nov 2022

- Develop an existing app and add some new feature in it.
- Fix and remove the bugs from an application.
- Technology Used Flutter, Dart, Cloud Messaging, GetX.